realitytvscandals.com 2018-04-05

# Privacy Policy | Reality TV Scandals

[**RealityTVScandals.com  ** ](http://realitytvscandals.com/ "RealityTVScandals")takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it. See this [privacy policy primer](http://cybec.com/what-is-a-privacy-policy/) to learn more about privacy policies in general.

## Routine Information Collection

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Where necessary, Produced Reality TV uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

## Controlling Your Privacy

**Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns.** Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms. This list of [web browser privacy management](http://cybec.com/web-browser-privacy-management/) links may also be useful.

## Special Note About Google Advertising

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to [opt out of Google’s cookie usage](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

## Special Note About Other Advertising

NOT ALL ADS ON THIS SITE ARE FROM GOOGLE..  WE ALSO USE CHITIKA, LUMINATE, ADCLICKMEDIA, Snip.ps (sharing links you may click “skip ad” at anytime)infolinks and blogvertise.

## Contact Information

Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to: admin@RealityTvScandals.com  for further clarification.  Additional contact information  for RealityTvScandals can be found on our [Contact ](http://www.realitytvscandals.com/contact-us/)page.

## Tracking Information

[RealityTvScandals](http://realitytvscandals.com/ "RealityTvScandals") may place a what is known as a traffic counter.  A traffic counter is a software that tracks, organizes traffic on a website.  It is used to help website owners determine where there traffic is coming from.  The software may be able to determine your I.P. location and or your location.  At the present time of this writing  **[RealityTVScandals.com](http://realitytvscandals.com/ "RealityTVScandals") **does not have any traffic trackers installed on the site; however, that may or can change at anytime.

As all pages  and posts  _[RealityTvScandals](http://realitytvscandals.com/ "RealityTvScandals")_  ; this page is subject to change at anytime without notice or warning.
